No good.
It's not budging at all.
W-Well, that was some decent force.
Is this guy for real?!
He could give Nanami-san a run for
his money in terms of physical blows.
Though I suppose that's why...
It's a rather sturdy veil.
We'll have to search for its weak point
and put a hole in it,
even if it's only for a second.
We can't get anywhere
without getting inside first.
Huh? Why not?
Why not?
Listen, this is a veil to keep sorcerers out.
It's a barrier.
Barriers are all designed to surround
you and protect yourself, right?
Which fundamentally means
that whoever lowered this veil
is inside it.
But back in Harajuku...
I see!
So staying outside the veil instead of
surrounding themselves with it increases
the risk of being discovered and defeated,
thereby raising the strength of the veil.
It's a real egg of Columbus idea.
Egg?
Though, man, they're completely ignoring
the fundamentals of barriers!
What a crazy idea!
Now I can see why the barrier didn't
break from Yuji's earlier blow.
If that's the logic,
the veil's source should be somewhere
that really stands out, right?
By increasing the risk of discovery,
they're further increasing
its strength, then?
Somewhere that stands out?
22:01 Shibuya Central Tower
Think the sorcerers will realize it?
This is the place that stands out
the most within the veil, right?
Probably.
But even if they do realize it...
Yeah.
The lower floors are swarming
with those transfigured humans.
They won't be able to
climb up here that fast.
Wires?!
These are great.
Do these bastards know
about the entrusted veil?
Good! Just as planned!
So this is the source of the veil?
Yeah. According to Mei-san,
it already has the barrier programmed in,
and it just needs someone
to pour cursed energy into it.
Which means as long as we destroy those,
we can ignore the curse users until later.
There were three of them?!
The veil keeping sorcerers
out is still active.
Where are the remaining two?
With him?!
Fushiguro! Dismiss Nue!
Grandson.
Yes, I know, Granny.
I have some endearing underclassmen now,
so it's time to earn some achievements here
so I can become a first-grade, too.
Fushiguro!
Where is he?!
Right there.
I didn't see the moment of impact.
His body is too clean.
Even if he is a sorcerer,
he plummeted from the 41st floor.
Get up, you old trickster!
Good grief.
Youngsters these days have
no pity for the elderly.
We can't waste time here.
It won't take long.
Episode 35
Seance
JUJUTSU KAISEN
Shibuya Incident
Why are you so insistent
on my recommendation?
You could easily become
semi-first-grade with your technique.
Because I believe it's important
to do things the right way.
Especially with bloody
work like being a sorcerer.
But I'm not that bright, so sometimes
I don't know what the right way is.
So whenever I'm at a loss, I think to myself,
"What would Nanami-san do?"
So it wouldn't be right to become
a first-grade without your approval.
Oh, would you like another drink?
A makgeolli.
Auspicious Beast Summon: #1,
Kaichi!
It's homing?
The Seance technique,
Auspicious Beast Summon.
By hiding his face, Ino can
become a spiritual medium
used to manifest the powers
of the four auspicious beasts.
Granny, that was...
Yes, quite the coincidence.
Number 2, Reiki.
Nanami-san entrusted those two to me,
so I can't just leave them alone,
but it would be a bad idea to
lead these two to them, too.
The best option is to kill them fast
and rejoin my underclassmen.
Adapt to the facts,
and maintain self-control.
Cast aside pride.
Honestly, matching pace with him
takes more effort than matching the enemy.
Itadori!
All good!
It's just a scratch!
So full of life.
What promising futures.
Makes it worth killing you.
Demon Dog's claws can
hurt even special-grades.
I hit him with serious force, too.
Then how...
is he not damaged at all?!
I thought this wouldn't take long?
No comment.
He's just as he seems—not all that strong.
But he's doing whatever it takes and
sacrificing himself to protect that old hag.
There's something more to them.
I should hurry up.
Their aura's changed!
We're all set now.
Got it, Granny.
I won't let you!
Zen'in Toji.
How is it, Grandson?
Yeah, it's great, Granny.
Better than any before.
JUJUTSU KAISEN
December 7th, 1989
Satoru Gojo Is Born
Happy birthday, Daddy.
Your present is seeing me in my uniform.
Isn't it cute?
I'm glad I went with Mori High after all.
That's all well and good,
but if you do this with that much confidence,
you'll turn out just like your mother.
Huh? Do you hate Mom?
I don't hate her,
but she did cheat on me.
Right.
Poor Daddy.
Who?
Honoka...
Where's my daughter?
I killed her.
I need a corpse in order to transform
into someone I've called.
It was her mother that she
screamed for when she died.
I'm sorry!
It ripped halfway through.
Please let me out of here!
Shut up.
Why are you doing this?
My job is killing people.
So I need to really understand
how the human body works.
We were
free.
The sorcerers had their hands
full with the cursed spirits
that had grown more active over the years.
As long as we did things right,
we could easily earn a living
without being tied down by anything.
We curse users were free to
live and do as we pleased.
Satoru Gojo?
Yes.
The child born to the Gojo
clan with the Six Eyes.
A kid?
The total bounty on his head is already
over a hundred million yen.
Oh, and this isn't a request.
It's first come first served.
Thank you for waiting.
Cursed spirits had been growing
stronger over the years...
And in that instant,
I understood exactly why!
Because of him! Satoru Gojo!
It was the same as when an insurmountable
track and field record was suddenly broken!
The same as when figure
skaters all started adding
more revolutions to their
jumps due to one athlete!
The balance of the world changed
when Satoru Gojo was born!
Quit looking at me, weakling.
We were free.
And in our later years,
that freedom was stolen from us!
Screw him!
I'll never retire!
I'll trample over the weak until the day I die!
This is fun!
Seriously, what is with this guy?!
It's not even about him
being tough at this point!
It's almost certainly the
result of his technique.
Is it damage nullification?
No...
Hey!
Satoru Gojo is here in Shibuya!
Why don't you leave those foundations for
the veil behind and get out while you can?!
What a lousy bluff.
"Gojo has been sealed."
You were the ones shouting that so loudly.
That's why we're out here having fun, you know.
If Gojo was still active,
we'd be sleeping at home.
I knew it.
He can't beat Gojo-sensei.
Fushiguro, you suck at lying.
So this guy's technique can't be
something as grand as nullification.
But that's okay.
That's okay!
Shut up.
If you don't want to fight,
then I'll kill you now.
Here he comes!
Fleeing Hares.
Fall back for now.
I've figured out his technique.
Transformation through Seance?
That hag is a medium?!
No, that's not the problem here.
What's up with him?
Is he some famous sorcerer?!
I can tell by his stance...
He's hella strong!
Number 4, Ryu!
The type of shikigami
that distracts with numbers?
So they're planning to launch a big attack
from the cover of these hares, huh?
They're gone!
They ran away?!
Max Elephant!
What the hell is this?
Appearing and disappearing...
Talk about restless.
If you're a man, be clear and decisive!
That stuff's not my role.
Huh?
What is with this brat's power?!
He's giving me chills!
For now, just keep attacking away.
This guy's engine is getting revved up, too!
Yes, yes!
A finishing blow!
My technique is Inverse.
While activated,
attacks that hit me are made
weaker the stronger they are,
and the weaker they are,
the stronger they become.
Not one person has ever managed to dodge my
counter after landing their finishing blow.
The more serious you two get,
the less chance you have against me!
I've figured out his technique.
It's probably Inverse.
The attack I threw out of sync
landed more effectively than your own.
Fleeing Hares isn't meant for offense,
but he didn't try to immediately
break through once he was surrounded.
I think that's also how he managed to stay
perfectly fine after slamming into the ground.
So we can defeat him with a forehead flick?
No, the attack can't be too weak.
If were just a pure inversion of force,
activating it would kill himself
with the minor force of air resistance.
True.
Since that doesn't happen,
there must be an upper and
a lower limit to his inversion.
Even with it activated,
he was still matching our attacks and
using cursed energy to defend from slashes
and the effects of our techniques, right?
Makes sense.
That also explains why he can't beat
an anomaly like Gojo-sensei,
and his technique's probably a bad
match against complex techniques, too.
Which means we need to strike together.
Hit him with a powerful attack and a
somewhat weak attack at the same time!
Yeah.
But we don't want him to realize
we've figured out his technique.
So we'll keep going at full power
and make a show of our crazy strength.
We'll start with a weak blow from Gama.
Then we pummel him with a rush.
When...
did they figure it out?!
But still...
Don't get cocky over that, you brats!
He stopped it?!
He killed his momentum for just a moment—
You're surprisingly adept.
Really?
So, did you hear that the Gojos'
little Satoru-kun was sealed?!
Huh? Oh, yes.
Ah, not interested?
Hey, you!
We heard this gossip from Geto-san there!
Oh, heavens me! How could I?
Please do forgive me!
Next time, "Blunt Knife."
Next Episode
Blunt Knife
Watch in a well-lit room from a safe distance.